burberryusaonline.com 2014-07-22

# Burberry - STORE

**Please read this privacy statement carefully. By accessing or using our website, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and unconditionally agree to be bound by the terms of this privacy statement and the terms and conditions on this website and any changes made to the foregoing. If you do not agree to this privacy statement, you are not authorized to use this website. You should check this statement regularly to see if any changes have been made.**

Last Updated: 1 June 2012

We have made changes to this Privacy Statement which are effective as of the above date. Please review this Privacy Statement and the changes herein carefully.

Burberry Limited, (who we refer to as "we", "us" and "our" below), take your privacy very seriously. This Privacy Statement explains what personal information and other data we collect from you through our website and through our stores and other business locations and activities including offline collection, how and when it is collected, what we use it for now and how we will use it in the future and details of the circumstances in which we may disclose it to third parties. If you provide your personal information to us offline, this Privacy Statement applies to our collection and use of your information. If you have any questions about the way in which your information is being collected or used which are not answered by this Privacy Statement and/or any complaints please contact us on [customerservice@burberry.com](mailto:customerservice@burberry.com).

By visiting and using [www.burberry.com](http://www.burberry.com/) (the “ **Website** ”)or any other application or website (“ **Application** ”) for the purchase or sampling of products from Burberry (as applicable) or providing personal information to us on the Website or any Application, you are consenting to the practices in relation to use and disclosure of your personal information described in this Privacy Statement and our Terms and Conditions.

If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, please obtain your parent's or guardian's consent before providing us with any personal information. This website is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 13. Any person who provides their information to us through the website or any other part of the website represents to us that they are 13 years of age or older.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW WILL WE USE IT?**

When you register for an account with us online, place an order with us or send us an enquiry, we will collect certain personal information from you, for example, your name, postal address, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, credit card numbers. We may also obtain information about you as a result of authentication or identity checks. We use this information to identify you as a customer, to process your order, to deliver products, to process payments, to update our records, to enable your use of interactive features of our service and to generally manage your account with us and to provide you with information by post, e-mail, mobile messaging, telephone communications and/or through any other digital means including social network platforms about our products, events, promotions and services. We may also use this information to tailor how our website appears to you and to tailor the contents of our communications with you, so as to make the website and those communications more relevant to you,

We may also at times ask you for other information, for example product size and category preferences, age and any special dates (such as birthday and anniversary) which will be used to enhance our service to you. Providing us with this sort of information is entirely voluntary, however we may not be able to process your order if you do not provide us with all the requested information.

We may collect and use non-personally identifiable statistical information about site traffic, sales and other usage related information, which we may share with third parties. Additionally, we may take personally identifiable information and de-identify it for our use or to share it in a de-identified or aggregated form with third parties to analyze usage, demographics, interests, performance, services, user experience, or for similar purposes.  We will not re-identify such data and we will ask our contracting parties to agree to keep the data in its de-identified form.

We may also use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, together with non-personal data to analyse, profile and monitor customer patterns so we can consistently improve products and services and understand what may be of interest to you and other customers.

In addition, for quality control and training purposes, we may monitor or record your communications with us. You agree to comply with all local laws, rules and regulations regarding online conduct and acceptable content.

**COOKIES AND HOW WE USE THEM**

Cookies are small pieces of information which are issued to your computer when you visit a website and which store and sometimes track information about your use of the website.  When you enter our site our web server sends a cookie to your computer which allows us to recognise your computer. By associating the identification numbers in the cookies with other customer information that you provide when for example you log-in to the site, then we know that the cookie information relates to you.

We use cookies to elevate your user experience and the quality of our site and service. This includes keeping track of what you have in your shopping bag, remembering you when you return to our site, identifying how you navigate around the internet, including where you click, and which website you arrived from.

By continuing to use this site, you consent to our cookie settings and agree that you understand our Cookies Policy which explains how you can manage your cookie choices and preferences. Please be aware that restricting cookies will impact on your user experience and may prevent you from using part of our site.

**HOW DO I UNSUBSCRIBE FROM BURBERRY EMAIL UPDATES?**

You agree that we are authorized to transmit email to you for the purpose of informing you about your particular transaction. In addition, if you provided your email address for registration with the Website, electronic newsletters, updates and promotional emails from Burberry and its affiliates, you agree that we are authorized to send informational and promotional emails to you.

If you receive email updates or promotional emails from us, and you no longer wish to receive these, you can remove your email address from our list by using the unsubscribe link which is included on all email updates, or by clicking here.

**ACCOUNT PASSWORD AND SECURITY**

The Website contains features that require registration. At the time you register for online account access, you may be required to select a username and password to be used in conjunction with your account. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password, if any, and are fully responsible for all uses of your password, whether by you or others. You agree to (a) log out of your account at the end of each session; (b) keep your password confidential and not share it with anyone else; and (c) immediately notify Burberry of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security. Burberry is authorized to act on instructions received through use of your password, and is not liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this Section.

**SUSPENSION AND TERMINATION RIGHTS**

Burberry reserves the right, at its sole discretion, immediately and without notice, to suspend or terminate your access to or registration on the Website for any reason, including without limitation any breach by you of these Terms. You agree that Burberry shall not be liable to you or any third party for any such suspension or termination.

**OTHER PEOPLE WHO MIGHT USE YOUR INFORMATION**

In certain circumstances we may share your information with affiliated companies including other companies in the Burberry group, joint ventures, franchisees, licensees and selected service providers who perform functions on our behalf such as fulfilling orders, processing payments, carrying out promotional services or data management. This includes the companies we have chosen to handle our order despatch service and any delivery company that we may use from time to time. We may also share your information with other companies who assist Burberry in promoting Burberry‘s products and services in order to provide you with enhanced customer services and/or share information about Burberry’s products and services with you. In each case, we will only provide these companies with the information which they need to carry out their services and they will not be permitted to use the information for other purposes. They will only be allowed to use your information in the way in which we instruct them. Burberry does not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

You also acknowledge and agree that in certain circumstances we may disclose personal information relating to you to third parties, for example, in order to conform to any requirements of law, to comply with any legal process, for the purposes of obtaining legal advice, for the purposes of credit risk reduction, to prevent and detect fraud and/or to protect and defend the rights, property and safety of Burberry and other members of our group, our website, our users, and others. We may reveal your information for the purposes of credit risk reduction and fraud prevention, and in such case, we will take steps reasonably necessary to protect the security of such information.

In the event that we or a part of our business undergo re-organisation or are sold to a third party, you agree that any personal information we hold about you may be transferred to that re-organised entity or third party.

We may transfer information that we collect from you to Burberry affiliated companies, including other companies in the Burberry group, joint ventures, franchisees, licensees and to service providers who perform functions on our behalf, based in countries outside of the United States of America and this information may be stored and processed in such countries. By submitting your personal data on the Website and/or any Applications you expressly consent to this transfer, storing and/or processing outside of the United States of America or any transfer of the information that we collect from you outside your country. In the event that we do transfer, store or process your personal data in a country outside the United States of America we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that the information is treated securely in accordance with this Privacy Statement and applicable data protection laws.

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you agree to comply with all applicable laws, rules and regulations regarding the transmission of data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.

**UPDATING AND REVIEWING YOUR PERSONAL DETAILS**

You can amend or update your information by logging into My Account on the Website and amending your details as appropriate. If you wish to remove your account or would like us to stop using your personal data for marketing purposes, then please email [customerservice@burberry.com](mailto:customerservice@burberry.com). For security purposes, we may request information to help verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your information.

We may retain original and updated information for reasons such as technical constraints, dispute resolution, troubleshooting, record retention, and enforcement of our agreements.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time. The amended Privacy Statement will be posted on the Website. We will indicate the date that this Privacy Statement was last updated. Any changes we make will be effective immediately upon update or notice, which we may provide by means including, without limitation, updating the Privacy Statement on the Website or posting a notice on the Website.

It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Statement frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so be sure to return to this page periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of this Privacy Statement. If we make changes to this Privacy Statement and you continue to use this Website or if you submit information to us following such changes, you will be deemed to have read and agreed to this Privacy Statement and any changes. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Statement and it supersedes any earlier version. We will only use personally identifiable information in accordance with the Privacy Statement that was in effect at the time the information was collected.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

The Website and/or applications may from time to time contain links to other websites not controlled by us. We do not accept responsibility or liability for the privacy practices, data collected or the content of such other websites. The operators of these linked websites are not under a duty to abide by this Privacy Statement. If there are terms and conditions, other privacy statements or policies appearing on those websites, you should also review them carefully as your use of those sites may be subject to them.

**SECURITY STATEMENT**

Unfortunately transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal data we cannot guarantee the security of your data submitted to our website and any transmission is at your own risk. While we strive to protect personal information, neither Burberry nor our service providers can guarantee the security of the information on and sent from our website, and are not responsible for the acts and omissions of any third parties who receive the information.

To help protect the privacy of the personal information you transmit through use of the website, Burberry uses reasonable administrative, physical and electronic security measures against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information. Personal information provided to Burberry via the Website or via any Applications and online credit card transactions are transmitted through a secure server using Secure Socket Layering (SSL), encryption technology. When the letters "http" in the URL change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL; also, your browser may give you a pop-up message that you are about to enter a secure area or display a padlock image.The Website and the Applications uses this encryption technology to protect your information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address and credit card number. Our customer service centre and stores also operate over a private, secure network. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

The Website and the Applications use this encryption technology to protect your information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, address and credit card number. Our customer service centre and stores also operate over a private, secure network. Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

However, please be aware that our website and services are run on software, hardware and networks, any component of which may, from time to time, require maintenance or experience problems or breaches of security beyond our control.

**GOVERNING LAW**

This Privacy Statement is governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws. Any action seeking legal or equitable relief arising out of or relating to the Website or this Privacy Statement shall be brought only in the courts of the State of New York or the United States District Court for the Southern District of New York.
